netpages.co.za 2016-11-27

# Privay Policy - NetPages

[Home](http://www.netpages.co.za/) » Privacy Policy

In the course of availing various services we provide from time to time through our website NetPages.co.za you may be required to give your name, residence address, workplace address, email address, date of birth, educational qualifications and similar Personal Information ("Personal Information"). The Personal Information is used for three general purposes: to customize the content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain services, and to contact you about our services. Unless otherwise stated explicitly, this Policy applies to Personal Information as disclosed on any of the Media.

We are committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of all Personal Information that you may share as a user of our services.

This policy does not apply to the practices of organizations that we do not own or to people that we do not employ or manage.

Personal Information will be kept confidential and will be used for our research, marketing, and strategic client analysis objectives and other internal business purposes only. We do not sell or rent Personal Information.

We will share Personal Information only if we have your consent or deemed consent to do so. After publishing your Personal Information, we cease to accept responsibility as how the other viewers may utilize your Personal Information. We have no control over who views online or print ads. Personal Information provided may be used to contact customers when necessary.

In furtherance of the confidentiality with which we treat Personal Information we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

We give you the ability to edit your account information and preferences at any time, including whether you want us to contact you about new services. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

You acknowledge that you are disclosing Personal Information voluntarily. Prior to the completion of any registration process on our website or prior to availing of any services offered on our website if you wish not to disclose any Personal Information you may refrain from doing so; however if you don't provide information that is requested it is possible that the registration process would be incomplete and/or you would not be able to avail of the our services.

If you have questions or concerns about these privacy policies; please send us an email at [privacy@netpages.co.za](mailto:privacy@netpages.co.za)
